https://www.zurinstitute.com/privacy-disclaimer-terms-of-use-dmca/

Skip to content
NewCustomer?
SIGN IN
Board Approvals
Private Practice Tools
Certificate Programs
Search for:
Sign In
New Customer?
Licensing Board Approvals
Search for:
Online CE Courses
Online Continuing Education for Mental Health Professionals - Over 125 Courses Offered
CE Courses by Subject
AbuseAddiction & Substance AbuseAging & End of Life IssuesArtificial Intelligence (AI) & Mental HealthAttachment Theory & TherapyChildren, Adolescents & ParentingCouples & SexualityCOVID-19Diagnosis & DSMDiversityDual RelationshipsEthics, Law, BoundariesHIPAAInternet & Web PsychologyIntimate Partner ViolenceMental Health Disorders & TreatmentsMindfulness, Meditation & CAMMotivational Interviewing & Performance PsychMovie-Based & Cinema TherapyNeuropsychology & NeurobiologySuicideSupervision & E-SupervisonTeleMental Health & Digital EthicsTherapeutic OrientationsTrauma and PTSD
Required Courses
Law & Ethics,Supervision,Aging,Child Abuse, Suicide,Domestic Violence...and more
Pre-Licensing Courses
Individual Courses for CA Pre-Licensure
Pre-Requisites for Psychologists in CA
Pre-Requisites for MFTs in CA
Pre-Requisites for LCSWs in CA
Pre-Requisites for LPCCs in CA
Multi-Course Savings
Pre-Licensing Courses
NEW COVID-19 FORM! >
Sorry, your browser doesn't support embedded videos.
Telehealth Billing in the Age of COVID 19 — and Beyond
A webinar with Barbara Griswold + FREE access to 1 CE course
More Info >
Live Case Consultation Group with Dr. Marty Klein
×
Sorry, your browser doesn't support embedded videos.
Zur Institute is pleased to announce our first LIVE Case Consultation Group. The series of five meetings will focus on couples’ therapy. In each 75-minute meeting two of the participating therapists will have the chance to present a case. While you watch or listen, each one will work with Dr. Marty Klein, who will ask unexpected questions, fearlessly role play, analyze the narratives, and stimulate new ways of thinking about each case. Participants can of course ask questions. You'll come away from each session looking at your own cases with fresh eyes.
When: Five Thursdays starting 9/17, continuing 10/1, 10/15, 10/29 and 11/12.
Live at 11-12:15pm Pacific Time.
Sessions will be recorded and available on-demand for two weeks after each session.
Cost: $95.00
To Register: Click Here
Close
Free Webinar!
×
For Everyone: General Public ~ Clients ~ Professionals – Please Share!
Back to School Amid COVID-19
Tips for the Emotional Well-Being of your Family
More than 50% of school age children report feeling socially isolated, anxious or depressed.
This free webinar is designed to support families navigate children's emotional reactions as they return to school, either in person or online. Dr. Alessandra Chiesa, a child psychologist, mother of two, and public speaker, will share suggestions for ways that parents and caregivers can help themselves and their children to better cope emotionally with challenges that emerge. Topics include:
Working with a child that resists schoolwork
Overcoming social isolation
What you can do if your child appears anxious or depressed
Managing your child’s (and your own) anxiety and worry
We will leave plenty of time for Q&A. If you can’t attend the live webinar, a recording will be available.
When: Sep 16, 2020 04:00 PM PDT/7PM EDT
Cost: Free
To Register: Click Here
Zur Institute has been providing Continuing Education to mental health professionals for over 25 years. We are extending this knowledge and wisdom to the general public through dynamic webinars on timely topics and our e-newsletter offering tips and resources for ways to best meet and manage challenges that arise in day-to-day living.
Close
Free CE Webinar!
×
Zur Institutepresents
Identifying Autistic Spectrum Disorder in Everyday Clinical Interactions
A Live Interactive Webinar
Thursday September 24th, 2020
2-3pm PDT/5-6pm EDT
This 1 credit course is developed for social work professionals. In this course, Theresa Regan, PhD will guide professionals to a better understanding of how to recognize clinical signs and symptoms of Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD) in everyday interactions.
Case presentations will serve to illustrate how clinicians can better recognize this condition and develop more effective strategies and interventions.
Target audience: This course is appropriate for all mental health professionals.
However, only social workers will receive continuing education credits.
Content level: beginning to intermediate
About the Instructor
Theresa Regan, Ph.D., is an adult neuropsychologist (specialist in brain-behavior relationships), parent of an amazing child on the autism spectrum, and certified autism specialist with the IBCCES. She brings validation, hope, and purpose to individuals and their families living on the autism spectrum.
With this mission at its core, she founded and directs the OSF HealthCare Adult Diagnostic Autism Clinic in central Illinois. Her books include Understanding Autism in Adults and Aging Adults and Understanding Autistic Behaviors. She is also author of the Zur Institute course Autism Spectrum Disorder: What Every Clinician Needs to Know.
Learning objectives
After attending this course, participants will be able to
Describe the benefits of an autism diagnosis at any age.
Identify features of autism in adolescent, adult, and aged adult clients.
Discuss red flags for autism spectrum disorder.
Identify therapeutic interventions for autistic clients to promote best outcomes.
Course outline
Introduction and rationale for this webinar
Overview of ASD
Polling Question
Clinical Case 1
Clinical Case 2
Polling Question
Clinical Case 3
Questions and Answers
Conclusion
Course interaction & system requirements
This live webinar is fully interactive. Attendees may ask and answer questions throughout the presentation and participate in instructor-led polls.
System requirements:
This webinar will be hosted through Zoom.
Upon registration, participants will be provided a link that they can use to access live from any desktop, laptop, tablet, or smart device.
Fee & registration
CLICK HERE TO REGISTER. Cost is free and includes 1 CE credit. Register by September 23rd.
Course completion & CE info
To earn CE credit, social workers must log in at the scheduled time and attend the entire session.
Upon completion of the webinar, participants will be provided information on how to sign up to
complete an online course evaluation and
immediately receive a CE certificate.
Zur Institute, provider # 1113, is approved to offer social work continuing education by the Association of Social Work Boards (ASWB) Approved Continuing Education (ACE) program. Organizations, not individual courses, are approved as ACE providers. State and provincial regulatory boards have the final authority to determine whether an individual course may be accepted for continuing education credit. Zur Institute maintains responsibility for this course. ACE provider approval period: 6/1/18-6/1/2021.
Social workers participating in this course receive 1.0 continuing education credits.
For questions, concerns, or to request special accommodations, please email support@zurinstitute.com
Close
Free Webinar!
×
Couple’s Therapy: When Substance Use is the Third Wheel
A Free Live Webinar
Friday, October 23rd, 2020
10-11am Pacific Time/1-2pm Eastern Time
Anxious about seeing couples when substance use is present? In this one-hour webinar, Diane McLendon LMFT, a seasoned couples’ therapist will provide participants with a conceptual framework that enhances efficacy when working with couples in which one partner struggles with substance use. The webinar will also provide practical tools and specific interventions to help clinicians develop confidence to better help their clients. Attendees will be able to ask questions throughout the presentation and participate in instructor-led polls.
Certificate of attendance will be provided to all participants who complete an evaluation at the end of the webinar.
No CE credits provided for this event.
Target audience: This course is appropriate for all mental health professionals.
Content level: beginning to intermediate
About the Instructor: Diane McLendon, LMFT, is a practicing therapist based in Portland, Oregon. In addition to her work providing couples therapy in addiction treatment facilities, Diane has codeveloped and facilitated a number or training programs for families, groups, and therapists focused on identifying and treating addiction.
She also co-created for the State of Oregon a multi-family group treatment program for persons with problematic gambling.
Learning objectives: After attending this webinar, participants will be able to:
Describe the framework of addiction and how it impacts the couple system.
Design interventions that meet the goal of increasing empathy and decreasing shame.
Apply specific techniques to shift the couple system and facilitate change.
Webinar outline
What addiction is (and isn’t)
Common myths of addiction
How to frame addiction
Biopsychosocial model of addiction: An intervention
Main goal: Increasing Empathy and Decreasing Shame
Interventions: The How To
Externalize, externalize, externalize!
Three’s a crowd
Personify and combat
Webinar interaction:
This live webinar is fully interactive. Attendees may ask questions throughout the presentation and participate in instructor-led polls.
DUE TO THE LIVE NATURE OF THIS PRESENTATION, NO RECORDING WILL BE AVAILABLE.
System requirements:
This webinar will be hosted through Zoom. Upon registration, participants will be provided a personalized link that they can use to access live from any desktop, laptop, tablet, or smart device.
This webinar is FREE but registration is required.
Register Now
To receive a certificate of attendance participants must log in at the scheduled time, attend the entire course and complete an online webinar evaluation. Certificate of attendance will be provided to all participants who complete an evaluation at the end of the webinar.
No CE credits provided for this event.
For Zur Institute Board Approvals go to
https://www.zurinstitute.com/licensing-board-approvals/
For questions or comments please email aviva@zurinstitute.com
ADA Policy and Grievance Procedure: Please see https://www.zurinstitute.com/ada-policy-grievance
Close
Free Webinar!
×
Post-Traumatic Growth – Building Strength Through Crisis
A Free Live Webinar
November 5th, 2020
2-3pm Pacific Time / 5-6pm Eastern Time
Uncertainty, adversity, and crisis, like we are facing today, is distressing, disruptive, and the cause of much anxiety about the future. But is it possible to grow through this crisis? This webinar addresses that very question. Introducing what is known as post-traumatic growth, we explore the ways in which crisis, trauma, and adversity can lay the foundation for prolific psychological growth.
Certificate of attendance will be provided to all participants who complete an evaluation at the end of the webinar.
No CE credits provided for this event.
Target audience: This webinar is geared specifically towards counselors, but is appropriate for all mental health professionals.
Content level: Intermediate
About the Instructor: Claire Nana LMFT is a licensed marriage and family therapist with over 15 years’ experience studying, writing about, and facilitating post-traumatic growth. She has worked in a variety of settings, including addiction treatment centers, private practice, and corporations. She has created 22 continuing education courses drawing on the fundamental concepts of post-traumatic growth and is also the author of Leverage: The Science of Turning Setbacks Into Springboards.
Learning objectives: After attending this webinar, participants will be able to:
Define post-traumatic growth
Discuss the fundamental components of post-traumatic growth
Describe the ways in which post-traumatic growth emerges through adversity and crisis
Summarize the ways in which post-traumatic growth can be enhanced and encouraged
Webinar outline
Introduction
What Is Post-Traumatic Growth?
The Five Components Of Growth
The Paradoxical Element Of Post-Traumatic Growth
How Growth Emerges Through Adversity
How We Can Encourage Post-Traumatic Growth In Time Of Crisis
Webinar interaction: This live webinar is fully interactive. Attendees may ask questions throughout the presentation and participate in instructor-led polls.
DUE TO THE LIVE NATURE OF THIS PRESENTATION, NO RECORDING WILL BE AVAILABLE.
System requirements: This webinar will be hosted through Zoom. Upon registration, participants will be provided a personalized link that they can use to access live from any desktop, laptop, tablet, or smart device.
This webinar is FREE but registration is required.
Register Now
To receive a certificate of attendance participants must log in at the scheduled time, attend the entire course and complete an online webinar evaluation. Certificate of attendance will be provided to all participants who complete an evaluation at the end of the webinar.
No CE credits provided for this event.
For Zur Institute Board Approvals go to
https://www.zurinstitute.com/licensing-board-approvals/
For questions or comments please email aviva@zurinstitute.com
ADA Policy and Grievance Procedure: Please see https://www.zurinstitute.com/ada-policy-grievance
Close
Free Webinar!
×
Ménage à trois: When substance use disorder is the third wheel in a relationship.
A Free Live Webinar
Friday, October 23rd, 2020
10-11am Pacific Time/1-2pm Eastern Tim
Anxious about seeing couples when substance use is present? In this one-hour webinar, Diane McLendon LMFT, a seasoned couples’ therapist will provide participants with a conceptual framework that enhances efficacy when working with couples in which one partner struggles with substance use. The webinar will also provide practical tools and specific interventions to help clinicians develop confidence to better help their clients. Attendees will be able to ask questions throughout the presentation and participate in instructor-led polls.
Certificate of attendance will be provided to all participants who complete an evaluation at the end of the webinar.
No CE credits provided for this event.
Target audience: This course is appropriate for all mental health professionals.
Content level: beginning to intermediate
About the Instructor
Diane McLendon, LMFT, is a practicing therapist based in Portland, Oregon. In addition to her work providing couples therapy in addiction treatment facilities, Diane has codeveloped and facilitated a number or training programs for families, groups, and therapists focused on identifying and treating addiction.
She also co-created for the State of Oregon a multi-family group treatment program for persons with problematic gambling.
Learning objectives
Describe the framework of addiction and how it impacts the couple system.
Design interventions that meet the goal of increasing empathy and decreasing shame.
Apply specific techniques to shift the couple system and facilitate change.
Webinar outline
What addiction is (and isn’t)
Common myths of addiction
How to frame addiction
Biopsychosocial model of addiction: An intervention
Main goal: Increasing Empathy and Decreasing Shame
Interventions: The How To
Externalize, externalize, externalize!
Three’s a crowd
Personify and combat
Course interaction:
This live webinar is fully interactive. Attendees may ask questions throughout the presentation and participate in instructor-led polls.
DUE TO THE LIVE NATURE OF THIS PRESENTATION, NO RECORDING WILL BE AVAILABLE.
System requirements:
This webinar will be hosted through Zoom. Upon registration, participants will be provided a personalized link that they can use to access live from any desktop, laptop, tablet, or smart device.
This webinar is FREE but registration is required: CLICK HERE TO REGISTER.
To receive a certificate of attendance:
To receive a certificate of attendance participants must log in at the scheduled time, attend the entire course and complete an online webinar evaluation. Certificate of attendance will be provided to all participants who complete an evaluation at the end of the webinar.
No CE credits provided for this event.
Zur Institute has been approved by NBCC as an Approved Continuing Education Provider, ACEP No. 6036.
For questions or comments please email aviva@zurinstitute.com
Close
New Customer?
×
In order to create an account, you must first order a course from our broad selection. Once you have made a selection, click the "Order Course" button. You will then be directed to create a new account.
Need more information?
Close
Community Forum
×
Topic: Therapy in a Time of Change: Building Resilience
When: Thursday June 25th, 2pm PDT/5pm EDT
Length: 75 minutes
Cost: Free
For more information and to register
CLICK HERE
Close
Privacy Statement, Disclaimer Terms of Use & DMCA
Table Of Contents
Privacy Policy ~ Disclaimer & Terms of Use ~ Grievance Procedure ~ DMCA Notice
Privacy Policy
Who We Are
The Zur Institute shares our users' concerns about safety and privacy while online. We are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of our visitors to our web site and subscribers to our newsletter. We strive to adhere to the highest standards of ethical practices in all of our operations and we are dedicated to protecting your privacy.
Visitors to our Website
ZurInstitute.com respects the privacy of our web site visitors. You provide us with your personal information when you purchase catalog items, online courses, or when you write to us. The information you provide to us with your order is used only by our Customer Service department and only for the purpose of fulfilling and tracking your order. When you write to us with comments and suggestions, we will respond to you and only you. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
How we use your data
Zur Institute, Inc. uses your personal data:
to provide goods and services to you;
to make a tailored website available to you;
to manage any registered account(s) that you hold with us;
to verify your identity;
for crime and fraud prevention, detection and related purposes;
with your agreement, to contact you electronically about promotional offers and products and services which we think may interest you;
for market research purposes - to better understand your needs;
to enable Zur Institute, Inc. to manage customer service interactions with you; and
where we have a legal right or duty to use or disclose your information (for example in relation to an investigation by a public authority or in a legal dispute).
Website Cookies
A cookie is a small piece of information that a web site transfers to an individual computer's hard drive for the purpose of keeping records. When you place an order on our site, we use a temporary cookie to keep track of what choices you've selected. We will never use a cookie to retrieve information from your computer.
Google Analytics
When someone visits https://www.zurinstitute.com, we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.
Clinical Updates Newsletter
As part of the registration process for courses, purchase of private practice materials and/or subscribing to our Clinical Updates, we collect personal information. We use that information for a few reasons: to tell you about items you’ve asked us to tell you about; to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information; to check our records are right and to check every now and then that you’re happy and satisfied. We don't rent or trade email lists with other organizations and businesses.
We use a third-party provider, Constant Contact, to deliver our Clinical Updates. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our Clinical Updates. For more information, please see Constant Contact’s
privacy notice. You can unsubscribe to our Clinical Updates at any time of the day or night by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails or by emailing our data protection officer at support@zurinstitute.com.
Third Parties
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
Access to your personal information
You are entitled to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold. Sign into your account and visit your Profile OR email your request to our data protection officer, Deborah Porter at support@zurinstitute.com.
Links to Other Web Sites
This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, you'll need to check that site's privacy statement.
Educational Software
Zur Institute, Inc's online learning management software for continuing professional education is provided by Rievent Technologies (www.rievent.com).
Advertising
The Zur Institute, Inc.'s website does not host or receive funding from advertising.
Special
Provisions Applicable to Users Outside the United States
We strive
to participate in a global community with consistent standards for everyone,
but we also strive to respect local, state, and federal laws. For users who
interact with Zur Institute, Inc. services outside the United States, know that
your personal data is transferred to and processed in the United States. The EU
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) applies to Zur Institute, Inc. and
its customers, as it applies to all companies processing the personal data of
data subjects residing in the EU, regardless of the company’s location.
Changes to this Privacy Notice
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes to our business or applicable laws.
The revised Privacy Policy will be effective as of the published effective date. This Privacy Policy was updated on February 7, 2019.
CE Conflicts of Interest
As an approved sponsor of continuing education, Zur Institute, Inc. is committed to the identification and resolution of potential conflicts of interest in the planning, promotion, delivery, and evaluation of continuing education. Consistent with concepts outlined in the APA Ethical Principles of Psychologists and Code of Conduct and other Associations' Codes of Ethics, potential conflicts of interest occur when an individual assumes a professional role in the planning, promotion, delivery, or evaluation of continuing education where personal, professional, legal, financial, or other interests could reasonably be expected to impair his or her objectivity, competence, or effectiveness.
Disclaimer & Terms of Use
The Zur Institute web site does not intend to be a substitute for legal, ethical or clinical advice or consultation or for treatment. The Zur Institute site is strictly educational. Readers must update themselves and follow their state laws and regulations and their profession's guidelines and regulations. This site expresses only The Zur Institute's opinion and understanding of the professional literature, standard of care and professional regulations. It neither gives advice regarding specific cases nor offers a definitive interpretation of any of the complex and often conflicting and ambiguous state and federal laws and regulations or professional standards or guidelines. Each individual case must be addressed separately and individually. Readers should always seek the advice of their physician or other qualified health provider with any questions they may have regarding a medical or mental health condition.
Laws, standards and guidelines, including HIPAA and other regulations, are continuously changing and evolving, and The Zur Institute site does not necessary reflect these changes. Readers should contact their professional association, malpractice insurance, state licensing boards and other state or federal agencies for the most current guidelines and information.
The content of courses and this site is for informational purposes only. Nothing contained in courses or this site is or should be considered or used as a substitute for professional medical or mental health advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Consult with a licensed, quality medical professional about diagnosis, treatment, and health care advice before a change or proposed change in a treatment plan. This website provides educational material on a variety of issues.
It is neither a substitute to medical or mental health treatment nor a substitute to calling 911 or emergency services. If you are feeling suicidal, thinking about hurting yourself, or are concerned that someone you know may be in danger of hurting himself or herself, call 911 or the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline at 1-800-273-TALK (1-800-273-8255). It is available 24 hours a day, 7 days a week and is staffed by certified crisis response professionals who may be be able to direct you to a crisis center in your area anytime 24/7.
Unless stated otherwise, all of The Zur Institute web pages on his site are copyrighted material and are not to be sold, distributed or shared by electronic or any other means. The Zur Institute has two types of web pages on his site: The first type is the publicly accessible web pages and the other type is the restricted web pages. The latter are the web pages that are accessible only after readers have paid for an online catalog item or an online course. The Zur Institute's publicly accessible web pages may be used or reproduced for the sole use of the individual reader. Links to The Zur Institute's publicly accessible pages can be posted on the web, unless these links are part of operations that are generating profit by using the material. In this case written permission from The Zur Institute is required. Posting or sharing the link to the restricted, non-publicly accessible web pages is not permitted. The written permission of the author is required for any other reproduction, transmission or use of the material or portion of the material.
The use of The Zur Institute's Site and Content is at your own risk. Unless otherwise prohibited by law, The Zur Institute will not be liable to you or to any other third party for: (a) any direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive or consequential losses or damages, including, but not limited to, loss of profits, loss of earnings, loss of business opportunities or personal injuries resulting directly or indirectly from use of information provided in The Zur Institute's site; or (b) any losses, claims, damages, expenses, liabilities or costs (including legal fees) resulting directly or indirectly from use of the material in these web pages. The conditions in this paragraph apply to any acts, omissions and negligence of The Zur Institute that would give rise to a course of legal action. The reader hereby agrees to indemnify and hold harmless The Zur Institute against all claims and expenses (including attorney fees) arising from the use of any information in The Zur Institute web site.
In order to access the online course material, it is the customer's responsibility to make sure they have the technology and, if necessary, the ability to seek tech support on their own. They have to make sure that their email service will accept and does not block emails from info@zurinstitute.com, support@zurinstitute.com, and orders@zurinstitute.com. As the online courses are designed to be a 100% web-based courses, The Zur Institute office neither faxes nor snail mails nor sends email attachments of any of the online course material.
It is illegal and unethical for anyone to receive more than one Certificate of Completion for each online course registration and to share with others any of the links or URLs to the course materials, evaluation, posttest or certificate web pages. These are only to be accessed by the person who paid and registered for the specific course and not by anyone else.
MCEP Reporting for California Psychologists
The Zur Institute's courses all meet the CA-BOP requirements.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or need further clarification, we're happy to help. Send email to The Zur Institute: support@zurinstitute.com or call us at 833-961-1344.
Grievance Procedure
Zur Institute, Inc. is fully committed to conducting all activities in strict conformance with the American Psychological Association's Ethical Principles of Psychologists. Zur Institute, Inc. will comply with all legal and ethical responsibilities to be non-discriminatory in promotional activities, program content and in the treatment of program participants. The monitoring and assessment of compliance with these standards will be the responsibility of the Director of Operations, Deborah Porter, in consultation with the members of the continuing education committee and Zur Institute, Inc.'s Ethics Chairperson.
While Zur Institute, Inc. goes to great lengths to assure fair treatment for all participants and attempts to anticipate problems, there will be occasional issues which come to the attention of the staff which require intervention and/or action on the part of the staff or an officer of Zur Institute, Inc.
This procedural description serves as a guideline for handling such grievances.
When a participant, either orally or in written format, files a grievance and expects action on the complaint, the following actions will be taken.
If the grievance concerns an author, the content presented by the author, or the style of presentation, the individual filing the grievance will be asked to put his/her comments in written format. The Director of Operations, Deborah Porter, will then pass on the comments to the author, assuring the confidentiality of the grieved individual.
If the grievance concerns Zur Institute, Inc. CE program, in a specific regard, the Director of Operations, Deborah Porter, will attempt to arbitrate. Zur Institute, Inc.’s policy is that the participant is welcome to exchange the course purchased if it does not meet their needs or receive full refund- no questions asked. If the participant would like a refund on a course not completed, please send an email to support@zurinstitute.com with your request. We will issue the refund and let the participant know we have done so. NOTE: we can only refund orders within 6 months of the date of purchase.
Digital Millennium Copyright Act Notice
Copyright Infringement Notification
If you believe that content available on or through the ZurInstitute.com Website, which is operated by Zur Institute, Inc. infringes one or more of your copyrights, please immediately notify Zur Institute, Inc.'s Copyright Agent by mail, email or fax ("Notification") providing the information described below. A copy of your Notification will be sent to the person responsible for the material addressed in the Notification.
Please be advised that you may be held liable for damages if you make material misrepresentations pursuant to federal law in a Notification. Thus, if you are not sure content located on or linked-to by the Website infringes your copyright, you should consider first contacting an attorney.
All Notifications should include the following:
A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site.
Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to locate the material.
Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted.
A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
Notifications should be sent to the following:
ZUR INSTITUTE, Inc.
Sign up for our Clinical Updates email and receive free resources.
Email Sign Up
